{
    "subject": "resource/Ran_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "Japanese",
    "human_readable": "The language of the film Ran is Japanese.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.673611044883728,
            "question": "What language was the film Ran made in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5701356530189514,
            "question": "How might the use of Japanese as the primary language affect viewers' understanding of the story and characters in Ran?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4751713275909424,
            "question": "Is the film Ran in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27702462673187256,
            "question": "What other elements besides language contribute to the cultural context of a film like Ran?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2048128843307495,
            "question": "Are there subtitles available for Ran in various languages?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14550910890102386,
            "question": "Could someone who doesn't speak Japanese understand Ran without subtitles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12928955256938934,
            "question": "Are there any films by Akira Kurosawa that are not in Japanese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11595343798398972,
            "question": "Why is it important to consider the language used in a film when analyzing its cultural impact?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07412896305322647,
            "question": "Could a film's message be conveyed differently if it were translated into another language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.053225401788949966,
            "question": "What are some examples of other films that utilize their original language to enhance storytelling?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of the film Ran is Japanese.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6857_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could a film's message be conveyed differently if it were translated into another language?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6857_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is it important to consider the language used in a film when analyzing its cultural impact?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6857_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any films by Akira Kurosawa that are not in Japanese?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6857_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6857_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6857_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6857_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6857_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6857_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6857_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6857_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6857_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6857_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6857_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation result:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`\n\nThe documents mention that \"Ran\" is a Japanese epic film directed by Akira Kurosawa, and also explicitly state that the title of the movie is Japanese for chaos or revolt, implying that the language of the film is indeed Japanese."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states, \"Ran (written and) is a 1985 film directed by Japanese Director Akira Kurosawa.\" Additionally, it mentions, \"'Ran\u2019 is n Japanese with English subtitles.\" This confirms that the language of the film Ran is indeed Japanese."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}